gulfbase.com 2010-12-29

# GulfBase.com - Privacy

| **Effective: October 29th, 2008**

Your privacy is important to us. Zughaibi & Kabbani General Partnership has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. This privacy policy governs the information collection practices of [ www.gulfbase.com](http://www.gulfbase.com/) .

We have established this Statement as a means to communicate our information gathering and dissemination practices to our customers and visitors. This online privacy policy describes how we use, disclose and protect personal information that you share with us. "Personal information" is information that enables us to identify you, such as your name and e-mail address. By using this Site, you agree to this Privacy Policy. 

GulfBase.com is a Licensee of the TRUSTe Privacy Program. TRUSTe is an independent organization whose mission is to build users trust and confidence in the internet by promoting the use of fair information practices. Because www.gulfbase.com wants to demonstrate its commitment to your privacy, it has agreed to disclose its information practices and have its privacy practices reviewed for compliance by TRUSTe. 

If you have any questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should first contact us at [feedback@gulfbase.com](mailto:feedback@gulfbase.com) . If you do not receive acknowledgement of your inquiry or your inquiry has not been satisfactorily addressed, you should contact TRUSTe at: 

[ http://watchdog.truste.com/pvr.php?page=complaint< /A>

TRUSTe will then serve as a liaison with us to resolve your concerns. 

](http://watchdog.truste.com/pvr.php?page=complaint)

---|---  
  
**Cookies**   
When you interact with the Site, we try to make that experience simple and meaningful. When you visit our Site, our Web server sends a cookie to your computer. Cookies are files that Web browsers place on a computer's hard drive and are used to indicate whether you have visited the Site previously. A "cookie" is a small piece of information sent by a Web server to store in a Web browser so that it can later be read back from that browser. Our Site uses cookies to keep track of a user's session.

**Choices about Cookies**  
You can configure your browser to accept all cookies, reject all cookies, or notify you when a cookie is set. (Each browser is different, so check the "Help" menu of your browser to learn how to change your cookie preferences.) 

We use cookies for a number of purposes, including to: access your account information when you "sign in," so that we can provide you with customized content; keep track of preferences you specify while you are using our Site and report our total audience size and traffic, and conduct research to improve our services to you. 

In order to make GulfBase.com a more valuable service for our subscribers and visitors, we may also collect and analyze statistical information. From time to time, we share this information in aggregate with a third party. However, this data is reported only in aggregate and reveals no personal details about individual visitors to our site. This information is distributed only to help attract appropriate advertisers for GulfBase.com site. 

**Advertisers**   
We use an outside ad company to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of our Web site, cookies received with banner ads are collected by our ad company, and we do not have access to this information. This privacy policy only governs the use of cookies by www.gulfbase.com 

**Clear Gifs (Web Beacons/Web Bugs)**   
Our third party advertising partners may employ a software technology called clear gifs (a.k.a. Web Beacons/Web Bugs), that help us better manage content on our site by informing us what content is effective. Clear gifs are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movements of Web users. In contrast to cookies, which are stored on a user's computer hard drive, clear gifs are embedded invisibly on Web pages and are about the size of the period at the end of this sentence. We do not tie the information gathered by clear gifs to our customers' personally identifiable information. 

**Registration Forms**   
Our site's registration form requires users to give us contact information (like their name, company name, email and postal address), and unique identifiers (like their user name). We also collect financial information at this point such as your credit card number, when you sign up for “Premium Membership” to service your request and complete your subscription request. 

Contact information from the registration forms is used to complete your subscription request, and to deliver information about our company. The customer's contact information is also used to get in touch with the customer when necessary such as in delivery of service requests, notifications or alerts that you have requested. These communications are generally not promotional in nature and you cannot opt-out of them. 

**Order Forms**   
Our site uses an order form for customers to request information, products, and services. We collect contact information (like their name, company name, email and postal address), and unique identifiers (like their user name). 

Contact information from the order forms are used to deliver orders, and information about our company. The customer's contact information is also used to send promotional material from some of our partners to our customers, and to get in touch with the visitor when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. 

Unique identifiers (such as user names) are collected from Web site visitors to verify the user's identity and for use as account references in our record system. 

**External Links**   
This site contains links to other sites. GulfBase.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. 

**Special Relationships**   
From time to time, GulfBase.com may offer special promotions through a partner. If you take advantage of a special offer, you are authorizing GulfBase.com to provide only that partner with the relevant information needed to fulfill the offer. 

**Security**   
This site has appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to protect against the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. This Site is hosted in a secure server environment that uses a firewall and other industry-standard technology to help prevent interference or access from outside intruders. This Site also requires that unique user names and passwords must be entered each time a customer logs on to the Site. We use SSL encryption {Secure Socket Layer} to ensure that users' sensitive information is protected and encrypted when processing credit card transactions. 

If you choose to use our referral service to tell a friend about our site, we will ask you for your friend's name and email address. We will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the site and register for a free trial account. This Site stores this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email and tracking the success of our referral program. 

**Third Party Agents**  
We may disclose your personal information to our third party contractors who perform services for our Site in order to complete or confirm your transaction or service request. We use a third party agent to process your credit card payments, as well as to send you newsletters from our site. These third parties are not authorized to use your information for their promotional purposes. 

This Site may disclose and transfer the information obtained from you through this Site as part of a merger, acquisition or other sale of its assets or business. In the event of such an occurrence, we shall notify you by a prominent notice on our site. 

Moreover, we may be legally obligated to disclose information to the government or to third parties under certain circumstances, such as illegal activity on our Site. www.gulfbase.com reserves the right to release personal information to its service providers, law enforcement or other government officials or in response to a formal request in a civil action, Court order or judicial proceeding as this Site, in our sole and absolute discretion, deems necessary or appropriate. 

**Choice/Opt-Out**   
Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out, at any time, of receiving promotional/marketing information from our partners. To opt-out:

• Log-in using your user name and password.  
• Go to “Home” in the top navigation menu and choose “Member Services”, then click on ["Update Personal Data".](http://www.gulfbase.com/site/interface/free/memberservices/updatepersonaldata.aspx) in the submenu.  
• Uncheck the options you would like to change.  
• Click on "Save Changes".

**Updating Personal Data**  
This site gives users the following options for reviewing, changing and/or modifying information previously provided: 

• Log-in using your user name and password.   
• Go to “Home” in the top navigation menu and choose “Member Services”, then click on ["Update Personal Data".](http://www.gulfbase.com/site/interface/free/memberservices/updatepersonaldata.aspx) in the submenu.  
• Make the necessary changes, and then click on "Save Changes".

**Contacting the Web Site**   
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, please send them to feedback@gulfbase.com or write to us at the following address: 

Zughaibi & Kabbani General Partnership (GB Privacy)  
19 Dar Elhejaz Building No. 1  
Tahlia Street, Jeddah, 21454  
Saudi Arabia  
Phone: +966 2 664 1264  
Fax: +966 2 660 3627

**Future Changes to our Privacy Statement**   
If we decide to change our privacy statement, it will be published on this page. If we make any material changes to this site, we shall notify you via email and a prominent notice on our site.
